Guide to the Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
Comic book collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Comic book collection, about 1984-2004.
8033
Andrew, Willett
5000 items.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 5,000 comic books published between 1984 and 2004.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Cornell University Class of 1992.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 5,000 comic books published between 1984 and 2004.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Willett, Andrew,
Subjects:
Comic books, strips, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See ComicBookDB.com for more specifics about comic book issues.
CONTAINER LIST
- 100%, 2002; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Paul Pope
  Artist/Penciler: Paul Pope
  Publisher: DC/Vertigo
  Notes: Five issue miniseries
- 100%, 2002; 2 (Box 1)
- 100%, 2002; 3 (Box 1)
- 100%, 2003; 4 (Box 1)
- 100%, 2003; 5 (Box 1)
- 1963, 1993; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Alan Moore
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Veitch
  Publisher: Image
  Notes: Six issue miniseries parody of silver age comics
- 1963, 1993; 2 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Bissette
- 1997 Direct Currents Special, 1997; - (Box 1)
  Publisher: DC
  Notes: Collaboration
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Jamie Delano
  Artist/Penciler: Frank Quietly
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 2 (Box 1)
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 3 (Box 1)
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 4 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: Warren Pleece
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 5 (Box 1)
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 6 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: James Romberger
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 7 (Box 1)
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 8 (Box 1)
- 2020 Visions, 1997; 9 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Pugh
- 2020 Visions, 1998; 10 (Box 1)
- 2099 Unlimited, 1994; 7 (Box 1)
  Author: Terry Kavanagh
  Artist/Penciler: Edmund Perryman
  Publisher: Marvel
  Notes: Features 2099 Fantastic Four
- 300, 1998; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Frank Miller
  Artist/Penciler: Frank Miller
  Publisher: Dark Horse
- 300, 1998; 2 (Box 1)
- 300, 1998; 3 (Box 1)
- 300, 1998; 4 (Box 1)
- 300, 1998; 5 (Box 1)
- 32 Pages, 1998; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Mark Crilley
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Crilley
  Publisher: Sirius
  Notes: Cover title: "Mark Crilley's 32 Pages"
- 9-11, 2001; Vol. 1 (Box 1)
  Notes: Trade paperback; Sept. 11th tribute collaboration
- 9-11, 2001; Vol. 2 (Box 1)
- Abadazad, 2004; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: J.M. DeMatteis
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Ploog
  Publisher: CrossGen
- Abadazad, 2004; 2 (Box 1)
- Abe Sapien: Drums of the Dead, 1998 (Box 1)
  Author: Brian McDonald
  Artist/Penciler: Derek Thompson
  Notes: Hellboy spinoff series
- Absolute Vertigo, 1995; 1 (Box 1)
- Accelerate, 2000; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Richard Kadrey
  Artist/Penciler: Pander Brothers
  Notes: Four issue miniseries
- Accelerate, 2000; 2 (Box 1)
- Accelerate, 2000; 3 (Box 1)
- Accelerate, 2000; 4 (Box 1)
- Action Comics, 1993; 685 (Box 1)
  Author: Roger Stern
  Artist/Penciler: Jackson Guice and Denis Rodier
  Notes: Special two issue arch "Funeral for a Friend" featuring Supergirl
- Action Comics, 1993; 686 (Box 1)
- Action Comics, 1994; 692 (Box 1)
- A Distant Soil [prospectus] (Box 1)
  Notes: Announcement for Neil Gaiman and Coleen Doran's "A Distant Soil", irregular size, stored on side of box
- Adventures in the DC Universe, 1997; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Steve Vance
  Artist/Penciler: John Delaney
- Adventures in the DC Universe, 1997; 3 (Box 1)
  Notes: Featuring Wonder Woman
- Adventures in the DC Universe, 1997; 10 (Box 1)
  Author: John Delaney
  Notes: Featuring the Legion of Super-Heroes
- Adventures in the DC Universe, 1997; Ann. 1 (Box 1)
  Notes: Annual featuring Impulse, Dr. Fate, Rose & Thorn, and Mr. Miracle
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 497 (Box 1)
  Author: Jerry Ordway
  Artist/Penciler: Tom Grummett
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 498 (Box 1)
  Notes: Special two issue arch "Funeral for a Friend"
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 499 (Box 1)
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 500 (Box 1)
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 500 (Box 1)
  Notes: Bagged deluxe ed.
- Adventures of Superman, 1993; 505 (Box 1)
  Author: Karl Kesel
- Adventures of Superman, 1996; 540 (Box 1)
  Author: Karl Kesel and Jerry Ordway
  Artist/Penciler: Terry Dodson
- Adventures of the Outsiders, 1986; 33 (Box 1)
  Author: Mike Barr
  Artist/Penciler: Alan Davis
  Notes: had been batman/outsiders; name change as of issue 33
- Adventures of the Outsiders, 1986; 34 (Box 1)
  Notes: Continuation of Batman and the Outsiders
- Adventures of the Outsiders, 1986; 36 (Box 1)
- Adventures of the Outsiders, 1986; 37 (Box 1)
- Adventures of the Outsiders, 1986; 38 (Box 1)
- Airtight Garage, 1993; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Moebius
  Artist/Penciler: Moebius
  Publisher: Marvel/Epic
  Notes: Cover title: Moebius' Airtight Garage
- Akiko, 1996; 2 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 3 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 4 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 5 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 6 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 7 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 8 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 9 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1996; 10 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 11 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 12 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 13 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 14 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 15 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 16 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 17 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 18 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 19 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 20 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1997; 21 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 22 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 23 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 24 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 25 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 26 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 28 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 29 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 30 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 31 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1998; 32 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 33 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 34 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 35 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 36 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 37 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 38 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 39 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 40 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 41 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 42 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 1999; 43 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 44 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 45 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 46 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 47 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 48 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 49 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 50 (Box 1)
- Akiko, 2000; 51 (Box 1)
- Akiko on the Planet Smoo, 2000 (Box 1)
- Alias, 2001; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Brian Michael Bendis
  Artist/Penciler: Michael Gaydos
  Publisher: Marvel/Max
- All-Star Comics, 1999; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: James Robinson and David Goyer
  Artist/Penciler: Michael Lark
  Notes: Two issue miniseries
- All-Star Comics, 1999; 2 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: William Rosado
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1983; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: John Byrne
  Artist/Penciler: John Byrne
  Notes: X-Men spinoff series
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1983; 2 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1983; 3 (Box 1)
  Notes: 2 copies
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1983; 4 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1983; 5 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 6 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 7 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 8 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 9 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 10 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 11 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 12 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 13 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 14 (Box 1)
  Notes: Sub-Mariner guest appearance
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 15 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1984; 16 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 17 (Box 1)
  Notes: X-Men guest appereance
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 18 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 19 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 20 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 21 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 22 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 23 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 24 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 25 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 26 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 27 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 28 (Box 1)
  Notes: Hulk guest appearance
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1985; 29 (Box 1)
  Author: Bill Mantlo
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Mignola and Gerry Talaoc
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 30 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 32 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 33 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 34 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 35 (Box 1)
- Alpha Flight (v.1), 1986; 36 (Box 1)
- Alphabet Supes, 1999; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Jim Krueger
  Artist/Penciler: Anthony Castrillo
  Publisher: Big Bad World Comics
- Amazing Adult Fantasy, 1962; 13 (Box 1)
  Author: Stan Lee
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Dikto
  Notes: Reprint ca. 1994
- Amazing Cynicalman, 1987; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Matt Feazell
  Artist/Penciler: Matt Feazell
  Notes: Zot! Spinoff series
- Amazing Spider-Man, 1968; Ann. 5 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: Larry Liber
- Amazon, 1996; 1 (Box 1)
  Artist/Penciler: Terry Austin
  Publisher: DC/Marvel
  Notes: Amalgam Comics event: DC/Marvel character mashups, Storm and Wonder-Woman
- Ambush Bug Nothing Special, 1992; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Keith Giffen
  Artist/Penciler: Keith Giffen
  Notes: Summer annual crossover
- America's Best Comics 64-Page Giant, 2000; 1 (Box 1)
  Publisher: Wildstorm
  Notes: Compilation
- Angela, 1994; 1 (Box 1)
  Author: Neil Gaiman
  Artist/Penciler: Greg Capullo
  Notes: Spawn spin-off
- Angela, 1994; 2 (Box 1)
- Angela, 1994; 3 (Box 1)
- Animal Man, 1992; 44 (Box 2)
  Author: Tom Veitch
  Artist/Penciler: Brett Ewins
- Animal Man, 1992; 45 (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Steve Dillon
- Animal Man, 1992; 51 (Box 2)
  Notes: "Flesh and Blood" six issue story arch revamps series
- Animal Man, 1992; 52 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1992; 53 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1992; 54 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 55 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 56 (Box 2)
  Notes: "Flesh and Blood" six issue story arch revamps series, 2 copies
- Animal Man, 1993; 57 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 58 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 59 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 60 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 61 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 62 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 63 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 64 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 65 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; 66 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 67 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 68 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 69 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 70 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 71 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 72 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 73 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 74 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 75 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 76 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 77 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1994; 78 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 79 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 80 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 81 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 82 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 83 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 84 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 85 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 86 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1995; 87 (Box 2)
- Animal Man, 1993; Ann. 1 (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Russel Braun
  Notes: Issue two of seven issue Children's Crusade crossover
- Animaniacs, 1996; 19 (Box 2)
  Author: Dave King
  Artist/Penciler: Charles Adlard
- Another Little Epic, 1990 (Box 2)
  Author: Scott McCloud
  Artist/Penciler: Scott McCloud
  Notes: Minicomic
- Aquaman (v.5), 1994; 0 (Box 2)
  Author: Peter David
  Artist/Penciler: Martin Egeland
  Notes: Zero Hour event issue; published between #2 and #3
- Aquaman (v.5), 1994; 1 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1994; 2 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1994; 3 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1994; 4 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 5 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 6 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 7 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 8 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 9 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 10 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 11 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 12 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 13 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 14 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 15 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 16 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; 17 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 18 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 19 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 20 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 21 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 22 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 23 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 24 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; 25 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 41 (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Jim Califiore
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 42 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 43 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 44 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 45 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1998; 46 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1995; Ann. 1 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.5), 1996; Ann. 2 (Box 2)
  Author: Ed Hannigan
- Aquaman (v.6), 2003; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Rick Veitch
  Artist/Penciler: Yvel Guichet
- Aquaman (v.6), 2003; 2 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.6), 2003; 3 (Box 2)
- Aquaman (v.6), 2003; 4 (Box 2)
- Aquaman: Time & Tide, TPB (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Kirk Jarvinen
- Arcana: The Books of Magic, 1994; A1 (Box 2)
  Author: John Ney Rieber
  Artist/Penciler: Peter Gross
  Notes: Issue six of seven issue Children's Crusade crossover. Came out immediately before Books of Magic #1; title lost 'Arcana' in the process
- Arion the Immortal, 1992; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Paul Kupperberg
  Artist/Penciler: Ron Wilson
- Arion the Immortal, 1992; 2 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Joss Whedon
  Artist/Penciler: John Cassaday
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 2 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 3 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 4 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 5 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 6 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 7 (Box 2)
- Astonishing X-Men, 2004; 8 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.1), 1995; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Kurt Busiek
  Artist/Penciler: Brent Anderson
- Astro City (v.1), 1995; 2 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.1), 1995; 3 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.1), 1995; 4 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.1), 1995; 5 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.1), 1996; 6 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1996; 1 (Box 2)
  Publisher: Homage
- Astro City (v.2), 1996; 2 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1996; 3 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1996; 4 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 5 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 6 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 7 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 8 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 9 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 10 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1997; 11 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1998; 12 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1998; 13 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1998; 14 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1998; 15 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1999; 16 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1999; 17 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1999; 18 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1999; 19 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 2000; 20 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 2000; 21 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 2000; 22 (Box 2)
- Astro City (v.2), 1998; 1/2 (Box 2)
- Astro City Special, 2004; 1 (Box 2)
  Notes: miniseries, pub. by wildstorm; cf. 'kurt busiek's astro city'
- Astro City: Local Heroes, 2003; 1 (Box 2)
- astro city: local heroes, 2003; 2 (Box 2)
  Notes: cf. 'kurt busiek's astro city'
- astro city: local heroes, 2003; 3 (Box 2)
- astro city: local heroes, 2003; 4 (Box 2)
- astro city: local heroes, 2003; 5 (Box 2)
- Asylum, 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Larry Marder
  Publisher: Maximum
  Notes: Double issue featuring Beanworld and Avengelyne
- Asylum, 2 (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Mark Buckingham
  Publisher: Millennium
  Notes: Compilation with Neil Gaiman, Mar Buckingham, P. Craig Russell, Faye Perozich, John Bolton
- Atom Special, The, 1995; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Tom Peyer
- Atom Special, The, 1995; 2 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Mike Allred
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Allred
  Publisher: AAA Pop
- Atomics, The, 2000; 2 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 3 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 4 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 5 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 6 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 7 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 8 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 9 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 10 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 11 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2000; 12 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2001; 13 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2001; 14 (Box 2)
- Atomics, The, 2001; 15 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Warren Ellis
  Artist/Penciler: Bryan Hitch
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 2 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 3 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 4 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 5 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 6 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 7 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 1999; 8 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 9 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 10 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 11 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 12 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 13 (Box 2)
  Author: Mark Millar
  Artist/Penciler: Frank Quitely
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 14 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 15 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 16 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 17 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 18 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; 19 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 20 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 21 (Box 2)
  Author: Brian Azzarello
  Artist/Penciler: Glenn Fabry
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 22 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 23 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 24 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 25 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2001; 26 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2002; 27 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2002; 28 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2002; 29 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.1), 2000; Ann. 2000 (Box 2)
- Authority, The (v.2), 2003; 1 (Box 2)
  Author: Robbie Morrison
  Artist/Penciler: Dwayne Turner
- Authority: Scorched Earth, 2003 (Box 2)
  Artist/Penciler: Frazer Irving
  Notes: one-shot
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1971; 88 (Box 3)
  Author: Harlan Ellison
  Artist/Penciler: Sal Buscema
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1979; 183 (Box 3)
  Author: David Michelinie
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1982; 221 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Bob Hall
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 227 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 232 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Allen Milgrom
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 233 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 234 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 235 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Bob Budiansky
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 236 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 237 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; 238 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 239 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 240 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 241 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 242 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 243 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 244 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 245 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 246 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 247 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 248 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 249 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; 250 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 251 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 252 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 253 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 254 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 255 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 256 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 257 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 258 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 260 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; 261 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1983; Ann. 12 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1984; Ann. 13 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.1), 1985; Ann. 14 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 1 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: George Perez
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 2 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 3 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 4 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 5 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 6 (Box 3)
- Avengers, The (v.3), 1998; 7 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1996; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Grant Morrison, Mark Millar
  Artist/Penciler: N. Steven Harris
- Aztek, 1996; 2 (Box 3)
  Notes: Featuring Green Lantern
- Aztek, 1996; 3 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1996; 4 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1996; 5 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1997; 6 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1997; 7 (Box 3)
  Notes: Featuring Batman
- Aztek, 1997; 8 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1997; 9 (Box 3)
- Aztek, 1997; 10 (Box 3)
- Babe, 1994; 1 (Box 3)
- Babe, 1994; 2 (Box 3)
- Babe, 1994; 3 (Box 3)
- Babe, 1994; 4 (Box 3)
- Babe 2, 1995; 1 (Box 3)
- Babe 2, 1995; 2 (Box 3)
- Bacchus Color Special, 1995; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Eddie Campbell
  Artist/Penciler: Eddie Campbell
  Notes: See also Eddie Campbell's Bacchus
- Bandy Man, 1996; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Stephan Petrucha
  Artist/Penciler: Jill Thompson
  Publisher: Caliber
- Batgirl Adventures, 1998; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Paul Dini
  Artist/Penciler: Rick Bruchett
- Batman, 1993; 492 (Box 3)
  Author: Doug Moench
  Artist/Penciler: Norm Breyfogle
  Notes: Special arch "Knightfall" issue #1
- Batman, 1993; 493 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Jim Aparo
  Notes: Special arch "Knightfall" issue #3
- Batman, 1993; 494 (Box 3)
  Notes: Special arch "Knightfall" issue #5
- Batman, 1993; 499 (Box 3)
  Notes: Special arch "Knightfall" issue #17
- Batman, 1993; 500 (Box 3)
  Notes: Special arch "Knightfall" issue #19, Collector's ed.
- Batman, 1996; 530 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Kelley Jones
  Notes: Special arch "The Deadman Connection", cover A
- Batman, 1996; 531 (Box 3)
- Batman, 1996; 532 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1994; 22 (Box 3)
  Author: Kelley Puckett
  Artist/Penciler: Mike Parobeck and Rick Burchett
- Batman Adventures, 1994; 24 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1994; 25 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1994; 26 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1994; 27 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 28 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 29 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 30 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 31 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 32 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 33 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 34 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 35 (Box 3)
  Author: Kelley Puckett and Ty Templeton
- Batman Adventures, 1995; 36 (Box 3)
  Author: Ty Templeton
- Batman Adventures, 1994; A1 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Bruce Timm
- Batman Adventures, 1995; A2 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures Holiday Special, 1995; 1 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures: Mad Love, 1994 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures: The lost years, 1998; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Hilary J. Bader
  Artist/Penciler: Bo Hampton
- Batman Adventures: The lost years, 1998; 2 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures: The lost years, 1998; 3 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures: The lost years, 1998; 4 (Box 3)
- Batman Adventures: The lost years, 1998; 5 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1995; 1 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Ty Templeton
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1995; 2 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 3 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 4 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 5 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Tim Harkins
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 6 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 7 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 8 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 9 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Brandon Kruse
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 10 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 11 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 12 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; 13 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 14 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 15 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 16 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 17 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 18 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 19 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 20 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 21 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Joe Staton
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 22 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 23 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 24 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; 25 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1996; Ann. 1 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures, 1997; Ann. 2 (Box 3)
- Batman and Robin Adventures: Subzero (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 1 (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 2 (Box 3)
  Artist/Penciler: Dave Taylor
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 3 (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 4 (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 5 (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1999; 6 (Box 3)
- Batman and Superman Adventures: World's Finest, 1997; TPB (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1983; 1 (Box 3)
  Author: Mike W. Barr
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1983; 2 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1983; 3 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1983; 4 (Box 3)
- Batman and the Outsiders, 1983; 5 (Box 3)